<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://limb-laboratory.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://limb-laboratory.ca/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-07-25T21:13:39+00:00</updated><id>https://limb-laboratory.ca/feed.xml</id><title type="html">LIMB Lab</title><subtitle>An engaging 1-5 sentence description of your lab.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">LIMB Lab Members to Present at ISB 2025 in Sweden</title><link href="https://limb-laboratory.ca/2025/07/25/example-post-1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="LIMB Lab Members to Present at ISB 2025 in Sweden" /><published>2025-07-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-07-25T21:10:56+00:00</updated><id>https://limb-laboratory.ca/2025/07/25/example-post-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://limb-laboratory.ca/2025/07/25/example-post-1.html"><![CDATA[<p>We’re excited to announce that two members of the LIMB Lab have been selected to present their research at the International Society of Biomechanics (ISB) conference in Sweden this year.</p>

<p>Robert will be presenting his work on the effect of total ankle replacement on ankle joint biomechanics. His study leverages dual fluoroscopy imaging to capture precise in vivo joint kinematics, providing valuable insight into how ankle replacements influence post-operative joint motion. This research is an important step toward improving patient outcomes and refining implant design.</p>

<p>Emily will share her study on the biomechanics of ankle-foot orthoses (AFOs). Her work investigates how different conditions (AFO, SHOD and barefoot) effect joint kinematics during stance phase. By analyzing joint motion, Emily’s research aims to inform better AFO prescriptions tailored to individual gait mechanics.</p>

<p>We are incredibly proud of Robert and Emily for representing the LIMB Lab at such a prestigious international conference. Their work reflects the lab’s commitment to advancing musculoskeletal health through imaging and biomechanics research.</p>

<p>Stay tuned for updates from Sweden — and congratulations to both researchers on this exciting opportunity!</p>]]></content><author><name>LIMB lab</name></author><category term="International Society of Biomechanics" /><category term="Biomechanics" /><category term="big data" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that two members of the LIMB Lab have been selected to present their research at the International Society of Biomechanics (ISB) conference in Sweden this year.]]></summary></entry></feed>